<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<messages> 
<set id="Distributed Leadership" l2l2tag="DISTRIBUTED_LEADERSHIP">
<message >Propose a new idea to help you explore a different direction</message>
<message behaviortag="NEW_IDEA_NOT_DISCUSSED">You need to see how new ideas are relevant and helpful to your current work</message>
<message behaviortag="DIVERGENCE_WITHOUT_CONVERGENCE">How could you improve your plan? Look at the group planning map together</message>
<message>Assign tasks to help you split the work equally.</message>
<message behaviortag="MEMBER_NOT_PLANNING">Has everyone contributed in planning the work?</message>
</set>
<set id="Mutual engagement" l2l2tag="MUTUAL_ENGAGEMENT">
<message behaviortag="MEMBER_NOT_PLANNING">Has everyone done the work they said they would do?</message>
<message behaviortag="MEMBER_NOT_DISCUSSING" >Has everyone contributed to the discussion?</message>
<message behaviortag="STRUGGLE_NOT_DISCUSSED">If you need some help with your work make sure you ask first the rest of the group</message>
<message>You seem to disagree. Have you all tried to understand each other's point of view and opinions?</message>
<message>When you disagree it may be time to redefine your group goals/attitudes/roles.</message>
<message>When you disagree you may want to ask for help from a third party.</message>
<message>Discuss why you disagree in LASAD explaining first what you found difficult.</message>
</set>
<set id="Peer Feedback" l2l2tag="PEER_FEEDBACK">
<message>Someone should look at the work of group ...  and offer some constructive feedback</message>
<message >You should share and compare your models.</message>
<message >Evaluate each other's solution by first revisiting the task</message>
<message behaviortag="PERCEIVED_SOLUTION_NOT_SHARED">Evaluate each other's solution to see how general they are</message>
<message behaviortag="SHARES_NOT_VIEWED">You should give feedback when someone shares their work</message>
</set>
<set id="Reflection" l2l2tag="REFLECTION">
<message>Revise your plan. Does it match your work so far?</message>
<message behaviortag="NOT_USING_ATTITUDES_OR_ROLES">Use the attitude/role cards to reflect on your work so far.</message>
<message behaviortag="DIVERGENCE_WITHOUT_CONVERGENCE">Consider what you need to do to work better as a team.</message>
<message behaviortag="POSITIVE_AND_NEGATIVE_LANDMARKS">Consider your best/worse moment as team so far.</message>
 </set>
</messages>
